legalbluebook.com 2018-05-09

# The Bluebook - Privacy Policy

### _Effective Date: February 15, 2008_

Werespect your privacy and are committed to protecting the privacy of yourpersonal information. To help you feel secure when visiting [http://www.legalbluebook.com/](http://bluebook.staged.hubbardone.com/)(the “Site”) and using all Site-related services and content, we have adoptedthe following privacy policy (“Policy”). We reserve the right to change theterms of this Policy at any time by posting the new Policy on the Site.  All changes to the Policy will be effectivewhen posted, and your continued use of the Site after any such revision isposted will be deemed acceptance of such changes.  It is important to review this Policyperiodically for the most current version. If you have questions or concernsregarding this Policy, you should contact us at [editor@legalbluebook.com](mailto:editor@legalbluebook.com?subject=Bluebook%20Online%20Privacy%20Policy).

## 1\. Collection and Use of Information 

Nopersonally identifiable information will be requested from you if you merelyvisit the Site. We will only collect personally identifiable information fromyou when you subscribe to the Site and/or purchase products sold on the Site.

Ifyou subscribe to the Site or make a purchase on the Site, we will ask for yourname, email address, credit card information, billing address, shipping address(if applicable) and phone number. This information will be used to process yoursubscription and/or purchase and, if needed, to contact you about yoursubscription and/or purchase.

Youagree and acknowledge that any request and/or payment made by you forsubscriptions, products, or services or other products via the Site may beprocessed by third parties other than us and, therefore, you expressly consentto our communication and distribution of your personally identifiable informationto such third parties. In the event of such communication and distribution, wewill require that any third party recipient agree that it cannot use thepersonally identifiable information in any manner other than to fulfill yourrequest and/or process your payment.

TheSite does not track, collect or distribute personally identifiable informationabout mere visitors to the Site. We regularly compile aggregate statistics thatshow the number of visitors to the Site, the requests we receive for particularinformation on the Site, and the Internet Service Providers that those requestscome from. We use these statistics to adapt and improve the Site to the needsand preferences of our visitors and subscribers.

Exceptas otherwise set forth in this Policy, we will not share, sell or rent yourpersonally identifiable information to any third party except when (1) you havebeen given an opportunity to “opt out” of sharing, selling, or renting suchinformation and have declined to exercise that right within the time periodprovided or (2) we legally are required to convey such information, for examplein response to subpoenas, court orders or other legal process requiring suchdisclosure.   

Wedo not seek to collect personally identifiable information from persons underthe age of 13.  If we are notified thatwe have received information from a person under the age of 13, uponverification, we will immediately delete this information from our servers.  Notification may be sent toeditor@legalbluebook.com.

## 

2\. Use of Cookies 

Youhave the right to reWe use cookies to enhance your use of the Site and to better adapt the Site to your preferences. Cookies enable us to show you the pages you have most recently visited from the Site, to gather specific information from your previous visits to the Site and to recall features that you may have customized on your browser. If you do not wish us to collect information via the cookies on your computer, you should configure your browser to choose not to have cookies stored; most browsers allow you to do this. 

We use Google Analytics to collect information on the use of this website.  Please visit [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) for more information. 

## 

3\. Managing Your Information 

Youhave the right to request correction or deletion of any or all your personallyidentifiable information collected by us via the Site. We will keep records ofyour personally identifiable information as long as it is reasonably necessaryfor the purposes described in this Policy. You have the right to request us todelete your account information, subject to our need to keep appropriatearchives for our business.  You can make allsuch requests under this section by contacting us at [support@legalbluebook.com](mailto:support@legalbluebook.com?subject=Bluebook%20Online%20Privacy%20Policy%20Request).

## 

4\. Confidentiality and Data Security 

Itis our policy that all personally identifiable information requested by theSite, such as your name, billing address, e-mail address or telephone number,will be treated as private and confidential. Any personally identifiableinformation that you provide to us via the Site is stored in a secure locationand is accessible only by our employees, as appropriate, or necessary thirdparties, and is used only for the purposes for which you provided suchinformation.

TheSite employs reasonable procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of yourpersonally identifiable information. We sometimes rely on third-party serviceproviders for the physical security of some of our computer hardware and theprocessing of payment information. We thoroughly review such third-party’ssecurity procedures and believe that their security procedures are adequate.

Thetransmission of data or information over the Internet via the Site is notsecure and is subject to possible interception, loss or alteration while intransit. While we use industry-standard precautions to safeguard your personallyidentifiable information, we cannot guarantee complete security, as completesecurity does not presently exist on the Internet. 

## 

5\. Third Party Websites  

Itmay be possible to access third-party websites from the Site.  These third-party websites are not subject tothe terms of this Policy.  To ensure yourunderstanding of how the third-party websites protect your privacy, pleasereview their respective policies.

## 

6\. Governing Law 

ThisPolicy and any legal action to enforce this Policy shall be governed exclusivelyby the internal laws of The Commonwealth of Massachusetts, without regard to conflictsof laws principles. By using this Site you agree to be subject to the exclusivejurisdiction of the state and federal courts of The Commonwealth ofMassachusetts.
